<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Uncategorized &#8211; MusicMania</title>
	<atom:link href="/product-category/uncategorized/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Be your own rockstar</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 12:35:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/cropped-Screenshot-2024-04-17-at-1.06.16-PM-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Uncategorized &#8211; MusicMania</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Guitar online lesson for abusolute beginners</title>
		<link>/product/guitar-online-lesson/</link>
					<comments>/product/guitar-online-lesson/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bianka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 13:57:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=1187</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This course is made for beginners, you will learn basics of gutiar playing, essential chords and strumming techniques to understand music theory. After this course you will have all the basics and be ready to start playing on your own.

After you purchase this online lesson you will recieve an e-mail with the online lesson modules.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Welcome to Introduction to Guitar
<ul>
<li>Welcome to Music Mania online guitar lessons! Before you begin the course, we will cover all the details about the course and what you&#8217;ll need to know to get the most out of your Online course.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Acoustic / Electric Guitar and the Basics
<ul>
<li>In this first lesson, we will take things slow. We will focus on how to choose the right guitar for you and what accessories are essential for any guitar player. We&#8217;ll also learn the parts of the guitar and get you comfortable with your instrument.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Getting Started: Fundamental Guitar Skills
<ul>
<li>In this lesson, you will learn how to tune and you will start playing your instrument from the ground up! Be patient and remember: focus on being accurate and play in consistent time with your metronome. These things are far more important than playing with speed.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>The Twelve Half Steps and Basic Notation
<ul>
<li>While you don’t need to be an expert on music theory to play guitar, it is important to know the basic building blocks of music. With this understanding, music will no longer be shrouded in mystery or complexity. This lesson presents fundamental musical ideas in a fun, non-intimidating way.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Scales: Construction and Fingerings
<ul>
<li>In this lesson, you will dig into scales. Don’t be intimidated. Some of you may have heard of, or practiced, scales. It might have been during piano lessons. Most likely it wasn’t very exciting for you. Hopefully you&#8217;ll find the approach to scales in lesson 4 much easier and even fun.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Chords: Building Easy Triads and Power Chords
<ul>
<li>In this lesson, you will use all of the skills you’ve gained from the previous lessons to build the foundation of harmony. You will play certain scale notes at the same time to create chords. Let&#8217;s look at why chords sound like they do, how to build them, how to easily play chords in open position, and how to play chords that you can move all around the neck.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Putting it All Together: The Pentatonic Scale and Songs
<ul>
<li>Now that you have the &#8220;science&#8221; of the guitar in your fingers, you will learn a couple of songs. You will do this by using melody (from the scales) and harmony (from the chords) we have learned. You will also learn an essential scale for playing melodies and soloing.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/product/guitar-online-lesson/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
